# YAUHENIYA ZIALENKA

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER



# **EDUCATION**

#### Front-End intern

**Eventizer StartUp** September, 2022 - now

#### Front-end/JS Course

The Rolling Scopes School June, 2022 -September,2023

#### **React Course**

The Rolling Scopes School October, 2023 -

### Family physician

January, 2024

Belarusian State Medical University 2013 - 2019

## **EXPERIENCE**

Junior Front-end developer 2022-now

freelance

2019-2022 Doctor

Hospital, MInsk

2018-2019 Nurse

Oncology Center, Minsk

Nurse 2017-2018

Hospital, MInsk

#### **EXPERTISE**

Html5, CSS3,

Scss

React. React Hooks Windows, MacOS

JavaScript,

Next.js

git, Github

TypeScript

react-router-dom,

npm, yarn

GraphQL

react-hook-form

Fetch

React Context

OOP

SPA

Grid, FlexBox

HTTP, HTTPS

Redux, RTK

firebase

Webpack

Responsive WEB

REST API

Vite

design

Jest, Vitest

**ESlint** 

Figma

eCommerce

## **PROFILE**

#### My name is Evgenia.

I'm 27 years old. I devoted 9 years to medicine and decided to change the field of activity. I finished Front-end and React courses in The Rolling Scopes School.

I easily assimilate information, learn quickly, can easily switch from one task to another, like to cope with non-standard situations. I'm stress resistant, calm and ready to action.

I'm looking for a job or internship in Front-end development. I'm interesting in reactive technologies, especially React.

## **LANGUAGES**

Russian, English - B2, French - B1 Polish(beginner)

## **PROJECTS**

https://evgueniazet.github.io/#/

https://commandor05-onlinestore.netlify.app/

https://graphiql-app-eoby.vercel.app/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/rs-css/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/shelter/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/songbird/

https://evgueniazet.github.io/cssBayan/ cssBayan/index.html

# CONTACTS

email: yauheniyazialenka@gmail.com **phone:** +375 25 773 74 30, +48 511 250 189 github: https://github.com/evgueniazet